shortpixel.com 2016-05-01

# ShortPixel - Privacy Policy

ShortPixel belongs to [PAGEPEEKER SRL](http://pagepeeker.com/), here collectively called the "Company". The Company respects your privacy rights and recognize the importance of protecting the Personal Information (as defined below) provided by you to us. This Privacy Policy describes how the Company collects, stores, and uses the Personal Information you provide to us through the Company's web sites and through telephone or e-mail communications you may have with us. This Privacy Policy also describes the choices available to you regarding the Company's use of the Personal Information you provide to us, and the actions you can take to access this information and request that the Company correct or delete it. 

#### Consent

By using the Company's web sites, you acknowledge that you have read this Privacy Policy and you consent to the practices described herein with respect to the Company's collection, use and disclosure the Personal Information provided by you to us. This is the Company's entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy in accordance with the terms herein at any time, which is why we encourage you to visit this page often, review this Privacy Policy frequently, and remain informed about any changes to it.   
If, after review, you still have questions about any portion of this Privacy Policy, please contact the Company using the contact information provided at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. 

### Information Collection and Use

#### Personal Information

"Personal Information" means information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, or other contact information, whether at work or at home. 

On all Company web sites that collect Personal Information, we specifically describe what information is required in order to provide you with the product, service, or feature you have requested. 

We collect Personal Information when you contact us, when you register with us, when you use our products and services, when you submit an order with us, when you visit our web sites or the web sites of certain of the Company's partners, and when you enter promotions and sweepstakes. 

#### Registration

When you register with us on this site, you first complete the on-line registration form, which requires you to create a username and password. During registration, you are also required to provide Personal Information, which may include name, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number, and credit card expiration date. We use this information so that we may contact you about the services and products on the site(s) in which you have expressed interest or requested and to facilitate the completion of an order. 

#### Promotions, Contests and Sweepstakes

From time-to-time, the Company may provide you the opportunity to participate in promotions, contests or sweepstakes on its web site(s). Such promotions, contests and sweepstakes will also be governed by the rules and regulations posted with such promotions, contests and sweepstakes. If you participate, you will be required to register with the Company, which will require you to provide certain Personal Information. Participation in these promotions, contests and sweepstakes is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to register and provide your Personal Information. The requested information typically includes contact information, such as name, shipping address, e-mail address, and telephone number. We will use this information to notify winners and award prizes. Additionally, during your registration process you may opt-in to receiving additional related communications from us. If you decide to opt-in, we will use the information provided to send you communications described throughout this Privacy Policy. 

#### Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to the Company's newsletter(s), we will use your name and e-mail address to send the newsletters to you. 

#### Other Information Collected

Some information may be collected automatically every time you visit the Company's web sites, such as cookies and computer information. In addition, information may be collected from other independent, third-party sources. We also collect information about which pages you visit within this site. This site visitation data is identified only by a unique URL. 

#### Cookies

The Company uses both session ID cookies and persistent cookies as part of its interaction with your browser. A cookie is an alphanumeric identifier (a file) that the Company's web sites transfer to your computer's hard drive through a web browser to enable its systems to recognize your browser for record-keeping purposes. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser, while a persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. 

We use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our web sites. We use persistent cookies to identify and track which sections of its web site you most often visit. We also use persistent cookies in areas of its web site where you must register, and where you are able to customize the information you see, so that you don't have to enter your preferences more than once. 

The Company uses Google Analytics, an ad tracking technology that is provided by Google. For more information Google Analytics, please visit https://www.google.com/analytics/ 

By configuring the options in your browser, you may control how cookies are processed by your system. However, if you decline the use of cookies you may not be able to use certain features on this site and you may be required to reenter the information required to complete an order during new or interrupted browser sessions. 

Some of the Company's business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on the site. We have no access to or control over these cookies (see "Third Party Advertising" and "Third Party Cookies" below). Accordingly, this Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by the Company only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

#### Log Files

As is true of most web sites, the Company gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet services provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. The Company uses this information to analyze trends, to screen for fraud, to administer the Company's sites, to track users' movements around the web sites and to gather demographic information about the Company's user base as a whole. 

#### Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

The Company employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that helps it better manage content on its web sites by informing the Company what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. The Company uses clear gifs in its HTML-based e-mails to inform itself of which e-mails have been opened by you. This allows the Company to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of the Company's marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these e-mails, please see "Choice and Opt-Out" section of this Privacy Policy. 

###### Information from Third Party Sources

To improve services and enhance personalization, the Company may periodically obtain information about you from other independent third party sources and add it to our account information. []()For example, when you visit a site on which the Company advertises, and click through such advertisement, the Company may place cookies on your computer. 

### Use of Information

#### Verification, Billing, and Order Status

The Company collects Personal Information to verify the accuracy of your name, billing address, shipping address, credit card number, and credit card expiration date provided, to screen for fraud, to bill you for products and services purchased and to pay you for products and services sold. The Company uses your e-mail address(es) to contact you regarding the status of your order when necessary and to send you a Receipt Purchase/Sale Confirmation and Order Shipping Notification. 

#### Special Offers and Updates

The Company collects information about which sections of its web site you visit most often, so that it can send you our newsletter and information about relevant offers, promotions, contests, and sweepstakes which may interest you. 

Accordingly, the Company will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, promotions and sweepstakes. 

#### Service-related Announcements

The Company may, but is not obligated, to send you strictly service-related announcements or rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For example, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an e-mail. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications since they are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you may have the option to deactivate your account. 

#### Research

We also collect information for research purposes and to provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. The Company uses the information collected for its own internal marketing and demographic studies to improve customer service and product offerings. 

#### Customer Service

We will communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the products and services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by e-mail, live chat or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. 

#### Preferences

The Company stores information that it collects through cookies, log files, and third party sources to create a profile of your preferences, in order to improve the content of the Company's web site for you. 

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

The Company does not sell or rent any of the information collected to third parties for any purposes, but it shares information with third parties as described below. 

#### Service Providers

The Company discloses the information collected to external service providers necessary to facilitate the following outsourced operations: address verification, credit card processing, fraud screening and order shipping. 

#### Compliance with Legal Authorities

As required by law, and to enforce customers' or the Company's legal rights, and to comply with local, state, federal and international law, the Company may disclose information to law enforcement agencies. 

#### Choice and Opt-Out

If you no longer wish to receive the Company's promotional communications, you may "opt-out" of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication. 

#### Links to Other Web Sites

There are several places throughout the Company's web sites that may link you to other web sites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. When you click through to these web sites, this Privacy Policy no longer applies. The Company recommends that you examine the privacy statements for all third party web sites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing your Personal Information. 

#### Storage and Security of Personal Information Storage

The Company stores the information it collects on computers located in a controlled, secure facility protected from physical or electronic unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. 

#### Security

The Company protects the privacy and integrity of the information it collects by employing appropriate administrative protocols, technical safeguards, and physical security controls designed to limit access, detect and prevent the unauthorized access, improper disclosure, alteration, or destruction of the information under its control. The Company transmits the information used by its external service providers for the specific outsourced operations listed above across public and private networks via recognized encryption technologies, such as by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information you input. 

Although the Company follows the procedures set forth above to protect the Personal Information submitted to the Company, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Thus, while the Company strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, the Company cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about the Company's security on its web sites, please feel free to contact us using the contact page on the site. 

#### Internet Fraud

The Company has a ZERO TOLERANCE policy for Internet fraud or any attempt to access or acquire customer or other information on its web sites via illegal or surreptitious means. The Company works with local, national, and international fraud investigation agencies and employs a variety of electronic and other means to discourage, detect, and intercept fraudulent activities. The Company aggressively prosecutes, to the fullest extent of the law; those perpetrators apprehended conducting fraudulent activities on its web site. 

Agencies with which the Company cooperates are: state and local police authorities, the United States Federal Bureau of Investigation, US and International Customs Agencies, and Interpol. 

#### International Transfer

Personal Information collected by the Company may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which the Company or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Company's web sites, you consent to any such transfer of Personal Information outside of your country. 

#### Children

The Company's sites are not intended for or directed to persons under the age of 13. The Company does not buy or sell products or services from or to children. Any person who provides their information to the Company through the Company's web sites represents to the Company that they are 13 years of age or older. 

#### Changes to this Statement

The Company will, from time-to-time, update this Privacy Policy, each time revising the last updated date at the top of the Privacy Policy and indicate the nature of the revisions within the statement. The Company will notify customers of material changes to this statement by e-mail or by placing prominent notice on its web site. 

#### Contact Information

You may contact the Company by using the contact form on the site.
